Guide to the Goddard-Riverside Community Center Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Predecessor Organizations
  - Subseries I.7: Riverside Community House
    - Executive Director Report, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies, 1947-49 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Financial Records: Audit Reports, 1942-58 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Financial Records: Financial Statements, 1939-41 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Financial Records: Financial Statements, 1942-43 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Flyers, 1945-53 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Fundraising, 1950-54 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Greater New York Fund, 1938-47 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Greater New York Fund, 1948-50 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Greater New York Fund, 1951-53 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - History, ca. 1950s (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Records, 1940-57 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - National Federation of Settlements, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Neighborhood Bazaar Committee, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - News Clippings, 1942, 1953 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Newsletters, 1946-53 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Press Releases, 1941-54 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Programs: Camp Reports, 1940, 1951 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Programs: Director's Reports, 1950-59 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Programs: Family Case File, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Programs: Group Leader Reports, 1953, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Programs: Junior Groups, [nd] (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Programs: Miscellaneous, 1949-54 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Programs: Personal Service Worker Reports, 1945-47, 1958-59 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Programs: Quarterly Report, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Programs: Riverside Boys, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Programs: Schedules, 1939, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Programs: Sixty Plus Group, 1954, 1957-58 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Programs: Statistical Reports, 1939-40 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Programs: Summer Program, 1949-51 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Real Estate-West 63rd Street, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Real Estate-West 69th Street, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Real Estate-West 87th Street, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Report-"An Opportunity to Develop Good Citizens,", ca. 1950s (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Report-"The House on 69th Street,", ca. 1940s (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Society for Christian Work, 1939-42 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Staff, 1943-47 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Turrell Fund, 1943-47 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Wilson School Consolidation, 1947-54 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Subseries I.8: Child Study Association of America/Wel-Met Inc.
    - Administration: Adult Book Committee, 1973-77 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Administration: Annual Meetings, 1972-74, 1977, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Administration: Association of Jewish Sponsored Camps, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Administration: Bequests, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Administration: Brochures, 1970s (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Administration: Building--Correspondence, 1975-77 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Administration: Building--East 89th Street, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Administration: By-Laws, 1972-83 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Administration: Certificate of Incorporation, 1973-83 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Administration: Certificate of Change of Purpose and Name, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Administration: Child Study Press, 1972-74 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Administration: Child Study Press, 1975-78 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Administration: Childrens Book Committee, 1972-85 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Administration: Community Council of Greater New York, 1973-76 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Administration: Conferences-Today's Family, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Administration: Conferences--Today's Family-Correspondencee, 1975-77 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Administration: Conferences--Today's Family-Planning Committee, 1976-77 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Administration: Conferences--Today's Family-Workshops, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      [See also Box 97]
    - Administration: Conferences--You, Your Child and Art, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Administration: Financial Statements., 1974-83 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Administration: Fundraising, 1972-77 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Administration: Greater New York Fund, 1973-74 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Administration: Greater New York Fund, 1975-77 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Administration: Histories, [nd] (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Administration: Iavarone Mortgage, 1979-82 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Administration: Lawsuit, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Administration: Library, 1972-75 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Administration: Merger, 1982-85 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Administration: Nearly New Thrift Shop, 1971-77 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Administration: New York State Board of Social Welfare, 1974-83 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Administration: Newsletters, 1972-73 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Administration: Organization Chart, [nd] (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Administration: Personnel, 1973-80 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Administration: Proposal for the Assumption of Assets and Liabilities, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Administration: Social Work Students--Sherman, 1975-76 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Administration: Social Work Students--Smith, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors: Committees-Art Benefit, 1973-75 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Board of Directors: Committees-Bazaar, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Board of Directors: Committees-Executive, 1973-78 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Board of Directors: Committees-Finance, 1973-74 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Board of Directors: Committees-Lists, 1972-74 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Board of Directors: Committees-Long Range Planning, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Board of Directors: Committees-Miscellaneous, 1973-75 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Board of Directors: Committees-Nominating, 1974-75 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Board of Directors: Committees-Public Policy, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors: Committees-Search, 1972-75 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors: Committees-Theater Benefit, 1974-75 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors: Committees-Winter Festival Planning, 1973-74 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors: Correspondence, 1972-76, 1982-85 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors: Fund, 1973-75 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors: Loans, 1976-77 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Boards of Directors--Members-Formerly CSAA: A-B, 1941-1976 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Boards of Directors--Members-Formerly CSAA: C-D, 1957-77 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Boards of Directors--Members-Formerly CSAA: F-J, 1961-77 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Boards of Directors--Members-Formerly CSAA: Karelsen, 1940-60 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Boards of Directors--Members-Formerly CSAA: Karelsen, 1961-76 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Members-Formerly CSAA: L-R, 1954-76 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Lazarus, 1959-75 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - S-T, 1966-76 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Straus, 1947-77 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - W-Z, 1952-76 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Whitehill, 1943-77 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Members: B, 1965-77 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - C-D, 1965-75 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Eichel, 1937; 1965-77 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - G-H, 1967-76 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Gardner, 1965-76 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - L-M, 1965-76 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Lebenson, 1965-74 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Portnoy, 1965-76 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Prager, 1965-74 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Reitman, 1965-74 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Rose, 1965-72 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - S-W, 1965-76 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Siegel, 1965-77 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Siff, 1967-77 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Solender, 1965-72 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - : Stein, Howard, 1965-77 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - : Stein, Zachary, 1963-74 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, 1973-75 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, 1976-78 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, 1983-85 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Rosters, 1973-77 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Camp: Barryville, 1975-85 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Beaver Brook, 1979-82 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Conference Center, 1975-76 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Camp Management Project, 1974-77 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Narrowsburg, 1977-80 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Program Suggestions, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Property Correspondence, 1975-84 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Registration Correspondence, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Reports, 1973-75 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Silver Lake, 1973-83 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Special Trips, 1973-75 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Staff Handbook, [nd] (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Statistical Reports, 1969-76 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Summer Food Service Program, 1976-77 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Timber Harvesting Program, 1977-83 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Vacations for the Aging, 1973-75 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Whitman Property, 1974-76 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Winter Camping, 1975-77 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Series II: Administration
  - Anniversary-75th, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Annual Meetings, 1960-69 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Annual Meetings, 1970-79 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Annual Meetings, 1980; 1982-91 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Annual Reports, 1959-60; 1962-80 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Benefits, 1962-69; 1979; 1985 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Brochures and Promotional Materials, 1961-80s (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Budgets, 1960-69 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Budgets, 1970-80 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Budgets, 1981-83 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Budgets, 1986-90 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Budgets, 1990-91 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Budgets, 1991-92 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - By-Laws, 1969; 1979 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Capital Expenditures, 1973-75 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Children's Health Service, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Corporate Certificates, 1959-74 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1959-60 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1961-64 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Five Year Plan, 1979-80 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising: Abrons Foundation, 1983-91 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising: Astor Foundation, 1974-90 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising: Badgeley Residuary Charitable Trust, 1984-91 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising: Barker Welfare Foundation, 1983-91 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Fundraising: Barth Foundation, 1980-91 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising: Bodman Foundation, 1982-91 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Fundraising: Booth Ferris Foundation, 1980-91 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising: Calder Foundation, 1971-91 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising: Chatlos Foundation, 1980-91 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising: Clark Foundation, 1980-91 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising: Community Service Society, 1983-88 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising: Consolidated Edison, 1986-91 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising: Contributions, 1977-86 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising: Cummings Memorial Fund, 1988-91 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising: Diamond Foundation, 1986-91 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Fundraising: Dodge Foundation, 1974-88 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising: Dreyfus Foundation, 1988-91 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Fundraising: Duke Biddle Foundation, 1980-91 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising: Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies, 1960-65 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising: Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies, 1983-91 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising: Frueauff Foundation, 1981-91 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising: Gateposts Foundation, 1983-88 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising: Goldman Foundation, 1982-88 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising: Grant Foundation, 1980-91 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising: Greater New York Fund, 1962-64 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising: Greater New York Fund, 1970-72 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising: Greater New York Fund, 1973-74 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising: Greater New York Fund, 1976-78 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising: Greater New York Fund, 1979-81 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising: Greater New York Fund, 1982-85 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising: Greater New York Fund, 1986-87 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising: Greater New York Fund, 1988-91 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising: Greater New York Fund--Management Grant, 1975-79 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising: Greenwall Foundation, 1988-91 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising: Havens Fund, 1977-85 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising: Hazen Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising: Hearst Foundation, 1979-91 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising: J.M. Foundation, 1980-88 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising: Kunstadter Family Foundations, 1983-86 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising: Lavanburg Corner House, 1980-91 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising: Lincoln Fund, 1983-91 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising: Miscellaneous Foundations (A-B), 1963-91 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Fundraising: Miscellaneous Foundations (C-E), 1971-91 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising: Miscellaneous Foundations (F-I), 1974-91 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising: Miscellaneous Foundations (J-M), 1978-91 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising: Miscellaneous Foundations (N-P), 1968-91 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising: Miscellaneous Foundations (R-S), 1974-91 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising: Miscellaneous Foundations (T-W), 1980-91 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising: Morgan Guaranty Trust Company, 1983-91 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising: National Endowment for the Arts, 1974-80 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising: New York Community Trust, 1968-91 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising: New York Foundation, 1983-89 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising: New York State Council on the Arts, 1973-78 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising: Noble Foundation, 1985-91 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising: John O'Donnell Company, 1976-82 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising: Pinkerton Foundation, 1981-91 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising: Public Appeals, 1974-75; 1983-94 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising: Reynolds Babcock Foundation, 1985-87 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising: Rubinstein Foundation, 1983-91 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising: Shakin Associates, 82-83 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising: Shakin Associates, 1984-85 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising: Shakin Associates, 1986-87 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising: Shakin Associates, 1988-89 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising: Shakin Associates, 1990-91 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising: Silverman Charitable Trust, 1983-91 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising: Surdna Foundation, 1974-91 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Fundraising: Sweepstakes, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising: Teagle Foundation, 1980-91 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising: Tuttle Fund, 1981-91 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising: Ulrick and Bay Foundation, 1981-87 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising: Uris Brothers Foundation, 1984-91 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising: Wallace Fund, 1982-91 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Goddard-Riverside Housing Corporation, 1960-82 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Goddard-Riverside Housing Corporation-Closing, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Goddard Towers Co-op, 1962-63 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Goddard Towers Co-op, 1964-69 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Greater New York Fund/Demographics Survey, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - History, ca. 1980 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Holiday Baskets, 1966-77 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    [***RESTRICTED***]
  - Insurance, 1976-80 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Legacies, 1961; 1966-79 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Manual, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Merger-Goddard Neighborhood Center, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Merger-Pioneer Youth Camp, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Merger-CSAA/Wel-Met, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - New York City Housing Authority, 1960s-80s (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Newsletter Committee, 1972-75 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters, 1961-94 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1959; 1977-89 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Organization Charts, 1962-80 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Personnel Practices, 1962-88 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Phelps House Dedication, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Real Estate--599 First Avenue, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Real Estate--West 87th Street, 1959-74 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Settlement House Centennial, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Settlement House Core Management Project, 1980-81 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Site #30, 1972-85 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Staff, 1962-80s (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Staff Meetings, 1963; 1974-77 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Volunteers, 1963; 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Series III: Board of Directors
  - Advisory Board, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Biographical Data, 1973-77 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Committees: Ad-Hoc, 1972-73 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Committees: AIDS Project, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Committees: Art Show, 1965-76; 1983 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Committees: Bazaar, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Committees: Boutique, 1970-71 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Committees: Building, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Committees: Camp, 1960-87 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Committees: Children and Families, 1986-87 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Committees: Creative Arts, 1965-76 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Committees: Day Care, 1966-73 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Committees: Executive, 1960-73 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Committees: Executive, 1974-79 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Committees: Executive, 1980-90 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Committees: Finance, 1961-90 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Committees: Foundation, 1966-71 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Committees: Gaities, 1972-74; 1977 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Committees: Group Work, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Committees: Housing, 1982-90 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Committees: Investment, 1964-70 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Committees: Lists and Charts, 1959-83 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Committees: Long Range Planning, 1959-69 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Committees: Nominating, 1964-74 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Committees: Nominating, 1975-90 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Committees: Personnel, 1965-73; 1989 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Committees: Program, 1961-76 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Committees: Public Support/Relations, 1959-76 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Committees: Search, February-March 1972 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Committees: Search, April-June 1972 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Committees: Service Council, 1967 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Committees: Structures, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Committees: Tennis Benefit, 1975-86 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Committees: Thrift Shops-Chairman, 1969-72 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Committees: Thrift Shops-Correspondence, 1965-77 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Committees: Thrift Shops-Financial Reports, 1959-79 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Committees: Thrift Shops-Membership Lists, 1970-71 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Committees: Thrift Shops-Minutes, 1962-71; 1974 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Committees: Thrift Shops-Miscellaneous, 1970-72 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Committees: Thrift Shops-Procedures, 1965-70 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Committees: Thrift Shops-Reports, 1965-70 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Committees: Thrift Shops-Volunteer Lists, 1969-72 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Committees: Thrift Shops-647 Thrift Shop-Correspondence, 1968-73 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Committees: Thrift Shops-647 Thrift Shop-Minutes, 1968-74 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Committees: Thrift Shops-647 Thrift Shop-Volunteers, 1969-72 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Committees: Thrift Shops-Everybody's Thrift Shop-Correspondence, 1969-74 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Committees: Thrift Shops-Everybody's Thrift Shop-Directors, 1969-79 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Committees: Thrift Shops-Everybody's Thrift Shop-History, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Committees: Thrift Shops-Everybody's Thrift Shop-Minutes, 1969-79 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Committees: Thrift Shops-Everybody's Thrift Shop-Volunteers, 1970-72 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Committees: Thrift Shops-Four Charities Thrift Shop, 1980-84 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Committees: Volunteer Development, 1966-71 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Contributions, 1978-82 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1959-86 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Manual, 1963 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Minutes (Joint), 1958-59 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1959-61 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1962-63 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1964-65 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1966-67 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, 1968-69 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, 1970-71 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1972-73 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1974-75 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1976-77 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1978-79 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1980,82 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1983-84 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1985-86 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1987-88 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1989-90 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Rosters, 1959-74 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Rosters, 1975-91 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Series IV: Executive Director Files, 1960-1994
  - Subseries IV.1: Tom Wolfe
    - Addiction Task Force, 1970-72 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Board of Education, 1959-63 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - College and Career Consultants, 1966-71 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Community Council of Greater New York, 1960-71 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Community Meetings, 1966-68 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Community School Board, 1971-72 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1965-71 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Ethical Culture Society, 1959-69 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Goddard-Riverside Approach to Systematic Planning (GRASP), 1969-70 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Haven Relief Fund, 1964 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Head Start, 1965 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Head Start, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Head Start, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - "Hercules" Proposal, [nd] (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Hudson Neighborhood Conservation Project, 1962-66 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Hudson Neighborhood Conservation Project, 1967-70 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Insurance Case, 1956-62 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Legislation, 1967-71 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Mental Health Committee, 1966-67 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Mid-West Side Community Corporation, 1966-67 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - National Federation of Settlements, 1964; 1971-72 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Neighborhood Councils, 1961-68 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Neighborhood Health Council, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Neighborhood Health Council, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Neighborhood Health Council, Jan-June 1969 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Neighborhood Health Council, July-Dec 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Phoenix Project-Correspondence, 1963-65 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Phoenix Project-Memos, 1963-64 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Phoenix Project-Memos, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Phoenix Project-Miscellaneous, 1962-65 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Phoenix Project-Proposals, 1962-65 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Phoenix Project-Staff, 1963-65 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Planetarium Neighborhood Council, 1962-66 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Police Programs-Community Action Project, 1964-66 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Police Programs-Funding, 1965-69 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Police Programs-Miscellaneous, 1966-69 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Police Programs-"Operation Friend,", 1964-66 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Police Programs-"Operation Friend,", 1967-72 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Police Programs-Police Study Group, 1965-66 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Police Programs-Puerto Rico Visit, 1965; 1967 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Program Reports, 1963-68 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Proposal-"Neighborhood Aid to Elderly Relocatees,", 1967 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Sixty Plus Club, 1964-70 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Strykers Bay Neighborhood Council, 1959-65 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Strykers Bay Neighborhood Council, 1966-67 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Strykers Bay neighborhood Council, 1968-71 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, 1962-70 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - West Side Planning Around Youth Services, 1964-65 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Subseries IV.2: Bernie Wohl